(Kazooing)
(Girl Voice) Baby
(Suddenly, wild brass appears)
(Girl Voice) Baby Baby
(Kazooing intensifies to the point
we may not be able to contain it)
(But why contain it?)
(Girl Voice) Baby × 10
(Funky stuff)
Holy sh*t!
I thought told y'all to sit down or get down
I'm about'a hit ground
When I'm in the box, my hits way out of this bounds
Nobody's topping me
(You know it, damn right)
Most of y'alls loving me
(Doing it all night)
Keeping my friends close,
and my foes closer
Things getting messy,
but I never lift the nose up
As I get older
See things slower
My enemies looking like kids,
and I'm the grown up
(Forget it!)
I'm the next masterpiece made
A new generation team,
a wicked beast "Ace"
But I'm the mister nice guy
See? I'm a wise guy
Not a mafioso, but I hustle like Mike
Lay low if you're feelin' me
I take these beats, freaks go crazy with me
So put 'em up in this base with me
So shake with the man, L to the J's, now follow me
(You feel like you are going to have a Kazoo time)
I thought told y'all to sit down or get down
I'm about'a hit ground
When I'm in the box, my hits way out of this bounds
Nobody's topping me
(You know it, damn right)
Most of y'alls loving me
(Doing it all night)
Keeping my friends close,
and my foes closer
Things getting messy,
but I never lift the nose up
As I get older
See things slower
My enemies looking like kids,
and I'm the grown up
(Forget it!)
(... let the funk pile up
in the streets!)
(Girl Voice) Baby × 10
(Funky stuff)